

### CONTACT



**VARUN PRATAP SINGH** 



+91 8285197964



vpratapsingh147@gmail.com



RZ A-3/132 Street no.-1 Durga Park New Delhi-110045

### **LANGUAGES**

HINDI

**ENGLISH** 

## **SKILLS**

ILLUSTRATOR

**PHOTOSHOP** 

**INDESIGN** 

COREL DRAW

PREMIERE



### **HOBBIES**









# **VARUN PRATAP SINGH GRAPHIC DESIGNER**

## **PROFILE**

Highly Creative and multi talented graphic designer with innovative experience in multimedia, marketing and print design. I have collaborated with creative team to design and produce computer generated artwork for marketing and promotional materials. participated in production of print and promotional items for key clients under direction of marketing department.

## **EDUCATION**

2015 - 2016

High School

Govt.Boys Sr. Sec school no.-1 Janak puri

2017 - 2018

Graphic designing

Arena Animation South Extension

2018 - 2019

Video Editina

Arena Animation South Extension

## **EXPERIENCE**

**FRESHER** 

2017 - 2018

Free Lancing Work

**Graphic Designing** 

2018 - 2019

Free Lancing Work

Video Editing